http://www.sipsupply.com/component/content/article/2-sip-supply/96-privacy-policy.html

SIP Supply - Polyurethane Structural Insulated Panels | Greenix Panels
Resources
What is a SIP?
GreenixPanel.com
Articles Privacy PolicyThis statement discloses the privacy practices for the SIPsupply.com web site.Because SIP Supply, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and agrees to notify you of: What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the web site The organization collecting the information How the information is used With whom the information may be shared What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SIP Supply's control How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. If you have any concerns about this statement, please contact us.Information Collection and UseSIP Supply, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. SIP Supply, LLC collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.RegistrationIn order to use this web site, a user may be asked  to complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address, phone number, zip code, and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. We may also ask for other identifying information that may act as a temporary password upon initial log in to the web site. This information is used during the activation process for establishing the user's identity.Orders/OrderingWe request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.Aggregate Statistical DataWe may collect aggregate personal profile data regarding our members. This is used to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This data is not linked to personally identifiable information such as name or email address. For example, we may use this data to determine that a certain percentage of purchases for a specific product were female.SharingWe may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.LinksThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SIP Supply is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.NewsletterIf a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. The newsletter will always include an option to unsubscribe to that service.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.SecurityThis website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing.While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure locked environment.Supplementation of InformationIn order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is sometimes necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit accounts, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user's credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed.Special OffersWe send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.Site and Service UpdatesWe also send the user site and service announcement updates. Site users are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.Correction/Updating Personal Information:To change, correct or update your personally identifiable information (such as your zip code), click on "Your Account" and select "Update Preferences". When all the information is correct, click on "Submit". Your changes will take effect immediately.Choice/Opt-outOur users are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or by clicking on "Your Account" and select "Update Preferences". There will be a selection for receiving email and newsletters. Select "No" and then select "Submit". Your changes will take effect immediately. If you wish to opt out of your Construction Club membership, please email us, and one of our customer service representatives will be happy to assist you.Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.Contact SIP SupplyContact UsRequest a Quote(770) 776-6198SIP Blog@sipsupplyLike UsStructural Insulated Panels Structural Insulated Panels, polyurethane core, metal
and wood energy efficient, cost effective, structurally superior custom designs, multi-family, residential, commercial, military SIP-ready plans, SIP home kits, affordable housing Multiple SIP Factory Locations, serving markets Worldwide Proudly Made in USA
More SIP Info
department_of_energy_on_structural_insualted_panels.html
Request a Quote
Contact Us
Custom SIP Homes
How to Order your SIP Home
GP/M Metal SIP
About SIP Supply
© 2003-2018 SIP Supply, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
